Guide to the New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education Records
1950-1973
RG 54
Yale University Divinity School Library
11
(27 boxes)
The papers constitute the official archive of the organization from its formation in 1967 until its dissolution in 1973. They contain detailed information about the local Christian ministries programs of various colleges and universities in New England. The input of the following denominations to these programs is documented: American Baptists, Christian Church (Disciples of Christ), Protestant Episcopal Church, United Church of Christ, United Methodist Church, United Presbyterian Church. The New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education was formed in 1967 to organize ecumenical ministries in place of the duplicating and competing denominational ministries in centers of higher education throughout the New England states. It worked closely with the University Christian Movement in New England, serving as the 'church agency' that provided funds and personnel for the 'student agency' as needed. It continued in its work of coordinating programs and raising funds for them until its dissolution in 1973.
New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
The New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education, Inc., officially organized in October, 1967, was created as a corporation responsible for coordinating and administrating, at the New England regional level, the ministry in higher education of the participating church bodies. Denominations participating included the American Baptists, Disciples of Christ, United Church of Christ, United Methodist Church, United Presbyterian Church, and Protestant Episcopal Church. The goals of the Commission were to organize ecumenical ministries in place of the duplicating and competing denominational ministries in centers of higher education, to update and improve local ministry organizations through consultations and local self-studies, to interpret the potential of ministry in higher education to local churches, and to recommend priorities for development. The duties of the area secretary and related staff involved coordinating the programs at a state or sub-area level, seeking and receiving funds from national and local sources, and disbursing these funds to the various denominational and united projects of the corporation. The N.E.U.M.H.E. worked closely with the University Christian Movement in New England, serving as the 'church agency' which provided funds and personnel for the 'student agency' as needed.
The Commission was restructured in 1971 due to economic necessity and changing program needs. Following this restructuring, the Commission became more decentralized and was less directly supported by national denominational bodies. The original committee structure and area secretary were replaced by a service team approach and a part-time administrative secretary.
Further decentralization and economic necessity led to the dissolution of the Commission as of January 31, 1974.
Scope and Contents
The records date from the Commission's planning stages in 1966 to its final meeting in November, 1973. Scattered documentary items in the collection date from as early as 1950. The papers include correspondence, reports and minutes,study papers, printed material, and financial material. The first five series date from the period before the Commission's restructuring in 1971 and were received in an organized state. The first folder of the collection contains an explanation of the filing system implemented in the first five series. Other than precautions taken for the preservation of the material, these records have been left as they were received. Only one folder from Series I, as described by the filing system memorandum, was received by the Library.
The last two series represent Commission materials that were received in an unorganized state. Series VI contains all non-financial records of the Commission from the period after its restructuring. Original folder headings have been retained for these records and the materials filed in alphabetical order according to these headings. Series VII contains financial records dating from 1966 to 1973. These records are arranged alphabetically by type of material.
Arrangement
I. National United Ministries in Higher Education, 1970-1971
II. New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education, Inc., 1961-1971
III. N.E.U.M.H.E. Committees, 1961-1971
IV. Higher Education Centers, 1960-1971
V. Regional Structures in New England, 1961-1973
VI. Post-restructuring files, 1966-1973
VII. Financial Material, 1966-1973
Baptists -- New England; Methodist Church -- New England; Presbyterian Church -- New England; Universities and colleges -- Religion; New England -- Church history -- Sources; Christian Church (Disciples of Christ) -- New England; Episcopal Church -- New England; New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education; United Church of Christ -- New England
- National U.M.H.E., 1970-1971; Series I
  - Explanation of filing system for Series I-V (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1 NS-P Personnel Applications, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- New England Commission U. M. H. E., Inc., 1961-1971; Series II
  - PC-M Corporation Minutes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2C-M, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2C-M1, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2C-M1, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2C-M2, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2C-M3, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2C-M3, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 2C-M4, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 2C-M4, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 2Ca Corporation Office -bonding papers, etc., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 2Ca-C -correspondence, general, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 2Ca-Ca -Conference centers, 1970,n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 2Ca-P -Property (inventories, eases, etc.), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 2-D Development of N.E.U.M.H.E. -history, 1950-1957, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 2Dc-L -conversations with other communions:Lutherans, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 2E-C Executive Committee-correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 2E-M1 -minutes, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 2E-M1 -minutes, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 2E-M2 -minutes, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- N.E.U.M.H.E. Committees, 1961-1971; Series III
  - Christian Faith and Higher Education Projects Committee (CHEP)
    - 3C-C -correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 3C-F -foundation directory, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 3C-Fa -alternative funding, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 3C-M -minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 3CP-1 -projects for funding:-Issues in Higher Education, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 3CP-3 -N.E. Center for Continuing Education, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 3CP-6 -Ecumenical Continuing Education Center (Yale), 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 3CP-8 -Professional Cont. Ed. Min. in Higher Ed., 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 3CP-5 -University of Maine Human Sciences and the Church, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 3CP-9a -correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 3CP-9b -conference, June, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 3CP-9c -conferences June, 1968 1968 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - 3CP-10a -University of Massachusetts, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - 3CP-11 -Metropolitan Ministries in Higher Education, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - 3CP-11 -Metropolitan Ministries in Higher Education, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - 3CP-12 -Crisis in Higher Education, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - 3CP-13 -Faculty conferences, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Finance and Budget Committee
    - 3F -procedures, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - 3F-C -correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - 3F-E -expense accounts, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - 3F-M1 -minutes, 1970 Jan-Jun (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - 3F-M1 -minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - 3F-M1a -conversations with local campuses regarding budgets, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - 3E-M1b -budget process, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - 3F-M1b -budget process, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - 3F-M1b -budget process, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - 3F-S -monthly statements, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - 3F-S1 -monthly statements, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - 3F-Sa -sample materials (fund raising), 1966-1971 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Personnel Committee
    - 3P-C -correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - 3P-M -minutes, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - 3P-M -minutes, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - 3Y-M1 -minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - 3P-N -N.E.U.M.H.E. membership, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - 3P-Pa -procedures for call/sample job descriptions, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - 3Y-S -staff: area and administrative secretaries-, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - 3P-S -staff: calenders, schedules, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - 3P-Sa -salary studies (by year), 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - 3P-Sb -salary studies (raw data), 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Program and Strategy Committee
    - 3Pa -policy and future, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - 3Pa-C -correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - 3Pa-M2 -minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - 3Pa-M1 -minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - 3Pa-M1 -minutes supplement: sub-area meetings, 1971 Feb (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - 3Pa-N -N.E. Collegium, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - 3Pa-Na -N.E. campus ministers, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - 3Pa-Nb -N.E. Board of Hi. Ed., 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - 3Pa-S -study of hi. ed. in N.E., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - 3PaS-C -study of hi. ed. in N.E.-Connecticut, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - 3PaS-M -Maine, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - 3PaS-Ma -Massachusetts, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - 3PaS-R -Rhode Island, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - 3PaS-V -Vermont, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - 3Pa-T -theological seminaries, 1967,n.d. (Box 9, Folder 86)
- Higher Education Centers, 1960-1971; Series IV
  - 4 -Campus reviews, procedures, guides, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - 4 -Sample constitutions and by-laws, 1967-1969,n.d. (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Connecticut
    - 4 -Greater Hartford Campus Ministry, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - 4 -Greater New Britain United Campus Ministry -budget, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - 4 -Greater New Britain United Campus Ministry-constitution, correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - 4 -Greater New Britain United Campus Ministry -minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - 4 -Greater New Britain United Campus Ministry-local self-study, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - 4 Greater Bridgeport Campus Ministry-budget, constitution, correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - 4 -minutes University of Connecticut, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - 4 University of Connecticut -budget, local self-study, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - 4 University of Connecticut-constitution, correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - 4 University of Connecticut -minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - 4 University of Connecticut -minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - 4 -U.M.H.E. in Greater New Haven -budget, constitution, correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - 4 -U.M.H.E. in Greater New Haven-minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - 4 -Wesleyan University, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Non-staffed institutions: 4 -Eastern Conn. State College, 1968-1971 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Non-staffed institutions: 4 -Manchester Community College, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Maine
    - 4 -University of Maine-constitution, correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - 4 -University of Maine-minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - 4 -University of Maine-budget, personnel,local self-study, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Non-staffed institutions: 4 -Farmington State College, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Massachusetts
    - 4 -Boston University -constitution, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - 4 -Boston University -correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - 4 -Boston University -minutes, 1967-1971 (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - -Boston University -budget, personnel, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - -Bridgewater State College -constitution, correspondence, budget, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - 4 -Bridgewater State College-minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - 5 -Bridgewater State College -self-study, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - 4 -Cambridge Ministry in Higher Education -constitution, budget, personnel, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - 4 -Cambridge Ministry in Higher Education-correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - 4 -Cambridge Ministry in Higher Education-minutes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - 4 -Cambridge Ministry in Higher Education -minutes, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - 4 -Cambridge Ministry in Higher Education-minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - 4 -Cambridge Ministry in Higher Education -history, 1960-1968 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - 4 -Cambridge Ministry in Higher Education-self-study, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - 4 University of Massachusetts -constitution, budget, personnel, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 123)
    - 4 University of Massachusetts-correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - 4 University of Massachusetts-minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 125)
    - 4 University of Massachusetts-self-study, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 126)
    - 4 Worcester Area Campus Ministry -constitutions budget, personnel, corres., 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - 4 Worcester Area Campus Ministry-minutess self-study, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - Non-staffed institutions: 4 -American International College, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - Non-staffed institutions: 4 -Back Bay Area, 1962-1970 (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Non-staffed institutions: 4 -Brandeis University, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - Non-staffed institutions 4 -Springfield College, S.M.T.I., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 132)
  - New Hampshire
    - 4 -Keene State College -constitution, budget, correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - 4 -Keene State College-minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - 4 -University of New Hampshire -constitution, budget, correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - 4 -University of New Hampshire-minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - 4 -University of New Hampshire-self-study, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - Non-staffed institutions: 4 -Dartmouth College; Franconia College; Plymouth State College, 1955-1970 (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - Rhode Island
    - 4 -United Campus Ministry of Brown University and the Rhode Island School of Design -constitution, budget, correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - 4 -United Campus Ministry of Brown University and the Rhode Island School of Design-minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - 4 -University of Rhode Island -constitution, budget, correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - 4 -University of Rhode Island-minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - 4 -University of Rhode Island-self-study, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - 4 -Rhode Island College, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Non-staffed institutions: 4 -Rhode Island Community College, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - Vermont
    - 4 -Council for Cooperative Christian Ministry at UVM -constitution, budget, correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - 4 -Council for Cooperative Christian Ministry at UVM-minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - 4 -Council for Cooperative Christian Ministry at UVM-self-study, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - Non-staffed institutions: 4 -Goddard College; Vermont College, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 149)
- Regional Structures, 1961-1973; Series V
  - 4- University Christian Movement in New England -constitution, budget, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 150)
  - 4- University Christian Movement in New England-minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 151)
  - 5-Consultation on Planning for Mission in New England, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 152)
  - 5-Consultation on Planning for Mission in New England, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 153)
  - Interdenominational Bodies
    - 5-Connecticut Committee for Campus Ministry, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 154)
    - 5 -Maine Council of Churches, 1965-1970 (Box 15, Folder 155)
    - 5-Massachusetts Council of Churches, 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 156)
    - 5-New Hampshire Council of Churches, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 157)
    - 5-Rhode Island Interdenominational Commission on Campus Ministry, 1965-1971 (Box 15, Folder 158)
    - 5 -Vermont Council of Churches, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 159)
  - Denominational Bodies
    - 5-American Baptist, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - 5-Connecticut Baptist State Convention, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 161)
    - 5-Maine Baptist State Convention, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 162)
    - 5-Massachusetts Baptist State Convention, 1973-1971 (Box 16, Folder 163)
    - 5-New Hampshire Baptist State Convention, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - 5-Rhode Island Baptist State Convention, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 165)
    - 5-Vermont Baptist State Convention, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 166)
    - 5-Christian Church (Disciples of Christ), 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 167)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 168)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -National Advisory Committee, 1966-1970 (Box 16, Folder 169)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Episcopal Society for Ministry in Higher Education, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 170)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Provincial Secretaries Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Province Secretary, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 172)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Diocese of Connecticut, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 173)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Diocese of Maine, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 174)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Diocese of Massachusetts, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 175)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Diocese of Western Massachusetts, 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 176)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Diocese of New Hampshire, 1967-1971 (Box 17, Folder 177)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Diocese of Rhode Island, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 178)
    - 5-Protestant Episcopal Church -Diocese of Vermont, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 179)
    - 5-United Church of Christ - National office, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 180)
    - 5-United Church of Christ -Connecticut Conference, 1969- 1970 (Box 17, Folder 181)
    - 5-United Church of Christ - Maine Conference, 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 182)
    - 5-United Church of Christ -Massachusetts Conference -correspondence, newsletters, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 183)
    - 5-United Church of Christ - Committee on Church and Education, 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 184)
    - 5-United Church of Christ -Metropolitan Boston Association, 1963-1967 (Box 17, Folder 185)
    - 5-United Church of Christ - New Hampshire Conference, 1961-1966 (Box 17, Folder 186)
    - 5-United Church of Christ - Rhode Island Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 187)
    - 5-United Church of Christ -Vermont Conference, 1967-1971 (Box 17, Folder 188)
    - 5-United Methodist Church - National office, 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 189)
    - 5-United Methodist Church - Maine Conference, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 190)
    - 5- United Methodist Church - New Hampshire Conference, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 191)
    - 5- United Methodist Church - New York Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 192)
    - 5-United Methodist Church -Southern New England Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 193)
    - 5-United Methodist Church -Troy Conference, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - 5 -United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. -Connecticut Valley Presbytery, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 195)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. -Boston Presbytery, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 196)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. -Northern New England Presbytery, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 197)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. -Providence, RI, Presbytery, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 198)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. - Synod of New England -bulletins, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 199)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. - Synod of New England -minutes, 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 200)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. - Synod of New England -correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 201)
- Post-Restructuring Files, 1966-1973; Series VI
  - 6-Corporation Notebook, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - -Correspondence of Walter Schenck- Incoming, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 203)
  - 6-Correspondence of Walter Schenck- Outgoing, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 204)
  - 6 -Current Commission Notes, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 205)
  - -Executive Committee, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 206)
  - 6-Executive Committee, 1972 Jan-May (Box 19, Folder 207)
  - 6-Executive Committee, 1972 Jun-Dec (Box 19, Folder 208)
  - 6-Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 209)
  - 6-Grant Proposals, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 210)
  - 6 -Group Conference Centers, 1971,n.d. (Box 20, Folder 211)
  - 6-Regional Files - Maine, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 212)
  - 6-Regional Files - Massachusetts: American Baptist, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 213)
  - 6-Regional Files - Massachusetts: Amherst, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 214)
  - 6-Regional Files - Massachusetts: Boston/Cambridge, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 215)
  - 6-Regional Files - Massachusetts: Bridgewater, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 216)
  - 6-Regional Files - Massachusetts: State Committee Organization, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 217)
  - 6-Regional Files - Massachusetts: Worcester, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 218)
  - 6-Regional Files - New Hampshire, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 219)
  - 6-Regional Files - Rhode Island, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 220)
  - 6-Regional Files - Vermont, 1971- 1973 (Box 20, Folder 221)
  - 6 -Program and Strategy Committee, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 222)
  - 6-Self-studies: Study papers, 1966-1972 (Box 21, Folder 223)
  - 6-University Christian Movement in New England, 1969-1973 (Box 21, Folder 224)
- Financial Material, 1966-1973; Series VII
  - 7-Audits, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 225)
  - 7-Bank Statements, Checks, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 226)
  - 7-Bank Statements, Checks, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 227)
  - 7 -Bank Statements, Checks, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 228)
  - 7-Bank Statements, Checks, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 229)
  - 7 -Budget information/requests, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 230)
  - 7-Budget information/requests, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 231)
  - 7-Budget information/requests, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 232)
  - 7-Budget information/requests, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 233)
  - 7-Budget information/requests, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 234)
  - 7 -Budget information/requests, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 235)
  - 7-Budget information/requests, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 236)
  - 7-Budget information/requests Finance and Budget Committee, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 237)
  - 7-correspondence, records, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 238)
  - 7-correspondence, records, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 239)
  - 7-correspondence, records, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 240)
  - 7-correspondence, records, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 241)
  - 7 -Fund raising and disbursement service team, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 242)
  - 7-Fund raising and disbursement service team, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 243)
  - 7-Monthly accomnts, 1967 Jan, Feb (Box 25, Folder 244)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1967 Mar, Apr (Box 25, Folder 245)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1967 May, Jun (Box 25, Folder 246)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1967 Jul, Aug (Box 25, Folder 247)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1967 Sep, Oct (Box 25, Folder 248)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1967 Nov, Dec (Box 25, Folder 249)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1968 Jan, Feb (Box 25, Folder 250)